NAEEM HAIDARI



Yeni Mahalle Zafer Sokak House No 3 Karabük, Turkey 🗣

engr.naeem.h2050@gmail.com @

05319139702 📞

Objective

As a public educator with nearly decade of experience, I am seeking the opportunity to serve as a high school principal in my local community. I am eager to use my proven leadership skills to continue the district's legacy of quality education and help prepare students for future success.

Experience

2010 - 2013 FVO (Future Vision Organization) Peshawar, Pakistan

Head Teacher (English Department)
Worked as English Teacher Part Time

2013 - 2015 AIMS (Apex Institute of Modern Science) Peshawar, Pakistan

English Instructor

Worked as English Teacher Part Time

2016 - 2017 The Shaksha Point English Language New Delhi India

Genral Manager

Worked full time as a general manager in order to help the staff members and controll of

all institution instructions.

Education

2006/2008 Bo Ali Sene English Language Center

Diploma in English Language

Α

2008 Qaid-e-Azam Degree College of Commerce Peshawar, Pakistan

FSC (Fuculty of Computer Science)

12 Grade

2010 Capital Degree College Peshawar, Pakistan

DBA (Diploma in Business Administration)

В

2012 Subhash Educational Complex Peshawar, Pakistan

HRM (Human Resource Management)

В

Skills

Languages Skill Dari Urdu Pashto English Turkish

Computer Skills Typing Ms Office Hardware and Software